Guide to the James Hazen Hyde Collection of Allegorical Prints of the Four Continents ca. 1500-ca.1900 PR 27
New-York Historical Society
- Series XIX: Allegorical, French
  - Aviation- New-York-Herald (JHH# 1581 / Enregistre# 1791) (Folder Portfolio 14-1A)
    20th Century American Reproductive print
    Artist: Printmaker: Publisher: Roche
  - L'Europe (JHH# 1725 / Enregistre# 1792) (Folder Portfolio 14-1A)
    Artist: Printmaker: Publisher: Bes et Dubreuil
  - L'Asie (JHH# 1726 / Enregistre# 1793) (Folder Portfolio 14-1A)
  - L'Afrique (JHH# 1727 / Enregistre# 1794) (Folder Portfolio 14-1A)
  - L'Amerique (JHH# 1728 / Enregistre# 1795) (Folder Portfolio 14-1A)
  - Le Grand Jeu de L'Oye (JHH# 1770 / Enregistre# 1796) (Folder Portfolio 14-1A)
    Artist: Printmaker: Publisher: Deckherr
  - Amerika (JHH# 1997 / Enregistre# 1797) (Folder Portfolio 14-1A)
    19th Century Austrian Lithograph, hand coloring
    Artist: J. Beaume Printmaker: L. Müller Publisher: L. Muller
  - L'America (JHH# 2070 / Enregistre# 1798) (Folder Portfolio 14-1A)
    Artist: Cinti Printmaker: Geoffroy Publisher: Cereghetti
  - L'Asie (JHH# 2071 / Enregistre# 1799) (Folder Portfolio 14-1A)
  - Bal du Grand Prix a l'Opera (JHH# 3486 / Enregistre# 1800), 1925 (Folder Portfolio 14-1A)
    20th Century French Color lithograph
    Artist: Dresa Printmaker: Publisher: Lapina
  - L'Amerique (JHH# 4034 / Enregistre# 1801) (Folder Portfolio 14-1A)
    Artist: Printmaker: Publisher: Dubreuil
  - Liberte Egalite Fraternite (JHH# 5102 / Enregistre# 1802) (Folder Portfolio 14-1A)
  - Sauvage de n'importe Ou (JHH# 5208 / Enregistre# 1803) (Folder Portfolio 14-1B)
    Artist: Gavarni Printmaker: Gavarni Publisher: Thierry Freres
  - On aura bien du mal a L'elever, cet enfant la! (JHH# 5210 / Enregistre# 1804) (Folder Portfolio 14-1B)
  - La Chasse au Sanglier (JHH# 6161 / Enregistre# 1806) (Folder Portfolio 14-1B)
  - La Chasse aux Tigres (JHH# 6162 / Enregistre# 1807) (Folder Portfolio 14-1B)
  - La Chasse aux Lions (JHH# 6163 / Enregistre# 1808) (Folder Portfolio 14-1B)
  - La Chasse au Bison (JHH# 6164 / Enregistre# 1809) (Folder Portfolio 14-1B)
  - L'Europe (JHH# 6455 / Enregistre# 1810) (Folder Portfolio 14-1B)
    Artist: N. Maurin Printmaker: Publisher: Bes et Dubreuil
  - L'Asie (JHH# 6456 / Enregistre# 1811) (Folder Portfolio 14-1B)
  - L'Afrique (JHH# 6457 / Enregistre# 1812) (Folder Portfolio 14-1B)
  - L'Amerique (JHH# 6458 / Enregistre# 1813) (Folder Portfolio 14-1B)
  - L'Europe (JHH# 6464 / Enregistre# 1814) (Folder Portfolio 14-1B)
    19th Century French Engraving (roulette)
    Artist: Charles Lemonnier Printmaker: Bertrand Publisher: Jean
  - L'Asie (JHH# 7202 / Enregistre# 1815) (Folder Portfolio 14-1B)
    Artist: V. Adam Printmaker: Lemercier Publisher: J. Bulla fils
  - L'Afrique (JHH# 7203 / Enregistre# 1816) (Folder Portfolio 14-1B)
  - Europe (JHH# 7384 / Enregistre# 1817) (Folder Portfolio 14-1B)
    Artist: N. Maurin Printmaker: Villain Publisher: Desmaisons fils., H. Jeannin.
  - Asie (JHH# 7385 / Enregistre# 1818) (Folder Portfolio 14-1B)
  - Afrique (JHH# 7386 / Enregistre# 1819) (Folder Portfolio 14-1B)
  - Amerique (JHH# 7387 / Enregistre# 1820) (Folder Portfolio 14-1B)
  - Types des Nations (JHH# 7648 / Enregistre# 1821) (Folder Portfolio 14-1B)
    Artist: G. Gostiaux Printmaker: G. Gostiaux Publisher: F. Sinnett
  - Europe (JHH# 7650 / Enregistre# 1822) (Folder Portfolio 14-1B)
    Artist: Honore Daumier Printmaker: Destouches Publisher:
  - L'Espece Humaine (JHH# 7716 / Enregistre# 1823) (Folder Portfolio 14-1B)
    19th Century French Reproductive print
- Series XX: Single Continents, French
  - L'Asie (JHH# 1126 / Enregistre# 1824) (Folder Portfolio 14-2)
    19th Century French Engraving, roulette, hand coloring
    Artist: Stimato Printmaker: Pamela Dautel Publisher: Dauty
  - L'Europe (JHH# 1413 / Enregistre# 1825) (Folder Portfolio 14-2)
    Artist: Printmaker: Publisher: A. Bes et F. Dubreuil
  - Aux bords de l'Ohio (JHH# 1697 / Enregistre# 1826) (Folder Portfolio 14-2)
    Artist: de Montaut Printmaker: Ch. Bargue Publisher: Becuet freres
  - [America] (JHH# 1714 / Enregistre# 1827) (Folder Portfolio 14-2)
    Artist: A. Mouilleron Printmaker: Publisher: Bertauts
  - Americaine (JHH# 1715 / Enregistre# 1828) (Folder Portfolio 14-2)
    Artist: Guerard Printmaker: Regnier Publisher: Lemercier, Benard et Comp.
  - L'Amerique (JHH# 1716 / Enregistre# 1829) (Folder Portfolio 14-2)
    Artist: E. Desmaison Printmaker: E. Desmaison Publisher: Jte. Bourmance
  - L'Amerique (JHH# 1718 / Enregistre# 1830), 1814 (Folder Portfolio 14-2)
    19th Century French Engraving
    Artist: F. Girard Printmaker: C. V. Kermand Publisher: Drouart
  - L'Europe (JHH# 1719 / Enregistre# 1831) (Folder Portfolio 14-2)
    Artist: Printmaker: Publisher: Agustoni
  - F. Cooper (JHH# 1720 / Enregistre# 1832) (Folder Portfolio 14-2)
    Artist: V. Adam Printmaker: Publisher: Ed. Rigo
  - Europe (JHH# 1729 / Enregistre# 1833) (Folder Portfolio 14-2)
    Artist: Printmaker: Betremieux Publisher: Lordereau
  - Asie (JHH# 1730 / Enregistre# 1834) (Folder Portfolio 14-2)
  - L'Amerique (JHH# 1734 / Enregistre# 1835) (Folder Portfolio 14-2)
    Artist: Napon Thomas Printmaker: Becquet Freres Publisher: Riboni
  - [Figures from a ballet on America] (JHH# 2053 / Enregistre# 1836), ca. 1820 (Folder Portfolio 14-2)
    19th Century French Aquatint, hand coloring
  - L'Afrique (JHH# 4679 / Enregistre# 1837) (Folder Portfolio 14-2)
  - Amerique (JHH# 6264 / Enregistre# 1838) (Folder Portfolio 14-2)
    Artist: Printmaker: Paul Legrand Publisher: Dopter
- Series XXI: Allegorical, Netherlands
  - Hernando Cortes (JHH# 136 / Enregistre# 1839) (Folder Portfolio 15A)
    17th Century Flemish Etching
    Artist: Gasper Bouttats Printmaker: Publisher:
  - Emblem of America (JHH# 153 / Enregistre# 1840) (Folder Portfolio 15A)
    Artist: G. Lairesse Printmaker: J. Glauber Publisher:
  - Europa (JHH# 154 / Enregistre# 1841) (Folder Portfolio 15A)
    17th Century Dutch Mezzotint
    Artist: I. Gole Printmaker: Publisher:
  - Asia (JHH# 155 / Enregistre# 1842) (Folder Portfolio 15A)
  - Africa (JHH# 156 / Enregistre# 1843) (Folder Portfolio 15A)
  - America (JHH# 157 / Enregistre# 1844) (Folder Portfolio 15A)
  - Europa (JHH# 176 / Enregistre# 1845) (Folder Portfolio 15A)
    Artist: C. Visscher Printmaker: C. Visscher Publisher:
  - Africa (JHH# 178 / Enregistre# 1846) (Folder Portfolio 15A)
    17th Century Dutch Engraving
  - Asia (JHH# 177 / Enregistre# 1847) (Folder Portfolio 15A)
  - America (JHH# 179 / Enregistre# 1848) (Folder Portfolio 15A)
  - Europa (JHH# 1438 / Enregistre# 1850) (Folder Portfolio 15A)
    Artist: C. Visscher Printmaker: C. Visscher Publisher: C. Visscher
  - Asia (JHH# 1439 / Enregistre# 1851) (Folder Portfolio 15A)
  - Africa (JHH# 1440 / Enregistre# 1852) (Folder Portfolio 15A)
  - America (JHH# 1441 / Enregistre# 1853) (Folder Portfolio 15A)
  - Anseris instar auem foelix habet India (JHH# 1998 / Enregistre# 1854) (Folder Portfolio 15A)
    Artist: Ioan. Stradanus Printmaker: Carol de Mallery Publisher: Philippe Galle
  - [Amsterdam Town Hall with Dutch Lions] (JHH# 1155 / Enregistre# 1855) (Folder Portfolio 15A)
    Artist: Joseph Mulder Printmaker: Publisher:
  - Europa (JHH# 3253 / Enregistre# 1863) (Folder Portfolio 15A)
    16th Century Flemish Engraving
    Artist: Balthasar Pegan Printmaker: Crispin van de Passe Publisher: Crispin van de Passe
  - Delitijs Asiam (JHH# 3254 / Enregistre# 1864) (Folder Portfolio 15A)
    Artist: Crispin van de Passe Printmaker: Crispin van de Passe Publisher: Crispin van de Passe
  - Africa (JHH# 3255 / Enregistre# 1865) (Folder Portfolio 15A)
  - America (JHH# 3256 / Enregistre# 1866) (Folder Portfolio 15A)
  - Europa (JHH# 3283 / Enregistre# 1867) (Folder Portfolio 15A)
    Artist: Phillippe Galle Printmaker: Philippe Galle Publisher: Philippe Galle
  - L'Asie (JHH# 3284 / Enregistre# 1868) (Folder Portfolio 15A)
  - America (JHH# 3285 / Enregistre# 1869) (Folder Portfolio 15A)
  - Africa (JHH# 3686 / Enregistre# 1870) (Folder Portfolio 15B)
    Artist: Storer Printmaker: Blanc Publisher:
  - India (JHH# 3687 / Enregistre# 1871) (Folder Portfolio 15B)
  - Nova Reperta (JHH# 4214 / Enregistre# 1872) (Folder Portfolio 15B)
    Artist: Ioan. Stradanus Printmaker: Publisher: Philippe Galle
  - Europa (JHH# 4694 / Enregistre# 1873) (Folder Portfolio 15B)
    Artist: Justus Danckerts Printmaker: Justus Danckerts Publisher: Justus Danckerts
  - Asia (JHH# 4695 / Enregistre# 1874) (Folder Portfolio 15B)
  - Africa (JHH# 4596 / Enregistre# 1875) (Folder Portfolio 15B)
  - America (JHH# 4697 / Enregistre# 1876) (Folder Portfolio 15B)
  - (JHH# 5045 / Enregistre# 1877) (Folder Portfolio 15B)
    Artist: Justus Danckerts[??] Printmaker: Publisher:
  - Andrea Doria Admiral del Mar (JHH# 5212 / Enregistre# 1878) (Folder Portfolio 15B)
  - De Historien van het Oude en Nieuwe Testament (JHH# 5453 / Enregistre# 1879) (Folder Portfolio 15B)
    17th Century Dutch Etching, hand coloring
    Artist: R. Hooghe Printmaker: Publisher: J. Lindenberg
  - Europa Veridica in Septentrione (JHH# 6096 / Enregistre# 1880) (Folder Portfolio 15B)
    Artist: C. Van den Broeck Printmaker: Publisher:
  - Africa garula ad Austrum (JHH# 6097 / Enregistre# 1881) (Folder Portfolio 15B)
  - America, Agresti ignorantia, in Occidence (JHH# 6098 / Enregistre# 1882) (Folder Portfolio 15B)
  - Treves-Kamer van Haar Hoog Mog. (JHH# 7404 / Enregistre# 1888) (Folder Portfolio 15B)
    Artist: M. Terwesten and G. v. Giefsen Printmaker: I.C. Philips Publisher: I.C. Philips
- Series XXII: Allegorical, German
  - L'Europe (JHH# 160 / Enregistre# 1889) (Folder Portfolio 16)
    Artist: Johan-Jakob Haid Printmaker: Johan-Jakob Haid Publisher: Haid, Johann Jacob, 1704-1767
  - L'Asie (JHH# 161 / Enregistre# 1890) (Folder Portfolio 16)
  - L'Afrique (JHH# 162 / Enregistre# 1891) (Folder Portfolio 16)
  - L'Amerique (JHH# 163 / Enregistre# 1892) (Folder Portfolio 16)
  - Europa (JHH# 517 / Enregistre# 1893) (Folder Portfolio 16)
    17th Century German Engraving
    Artist: Paul Furst Printmaker: Paul Furst Publisher:
  - Asia (JHH# 518 / Enregistre# 1894) (Folder Portfolio 16)
  - Africa (JHH# 519 / Enregistre# 1895) (Folder Portfolio 16)
  - America (JHH# 520 / Enregistre# 1896) (Folder Portfolio 16)
  - Receptions Schein (JHH# 1311 / Enregistre# 1897), 1743 (Folder Portfolio 16)
    Artist: F. G. Schmidt Printmaker: F.G.Schmidt Publisher: Berolini
  - America (JHH# 1496 / Enregistre# 1898) (Folder Portfolio 16)
    Artist: Printmaker: Publisher: E.G. May and Sons
  - Brundliche und richtige anneissung wieman aus (JHH# 1695 / Enregistre# 1899) (Folder Portfolio 16)
  - Europaische Jagt (JHH# 2878 / Enregistre# 1900) (Folder Portfolio 16)
    18th Century Swiss ? Mezzotint
    Artist: T. H. Thoman Printmaker: Publisher:
  - Asiatische Jagt (JHH# 2879 / Enregistre# 1901) (Folder Portfolio 16)
    Artist: I. H. Thoman Printmaker: Publisher:
  - Africanische Jagt (JHH# 2880 / Enregistre# 1902) (Folder Portfolio 16)
  - Americanische Jagt (JHH# 2881 / Enregistre# 1903) (Folder Portfolio 16)
  - Europa (JHH# 4025 / Enregistre# 1904) (Folder Portfolio 16)
    18th Century Austrian Etching stipple, hand coloring
    Artist: Printmaker: Publisher: Tesaro
  - Asia (JHH# 4026 / Enregistre# 1905) (Folder Portfolio 16)
  - Africa (JHH# 4027 / Enregistre# 1906) (Folder Portfolio 16)
  - America (JHH# 4028 / Enregistre# 1907) (Folder Portfolio 16)
  - Europa (JHH# 4547 / Enregistre# 1908) (Folder Portfolio 16)
    17th Century Austrian Etching
    Artist: Ioh. Martin Will Printmaker: Ioh. Martin Will Publisher:
  - Asia (JHH# 4548 / Enregistre# 1909) (Folder Portfolio 16)
  - Africa (JHH# 4549 / Enregistre# 1910) (Folder Portfolio 16)
  - America (JHH# 4550 / Enregistre# 1911) (Folder Portfolio 16)
  - Europa (JHH# 5634 / Enregistre# 1912) (Folder Portfolio 16)
    18th Century German Etching, hand coloring
    Artist: Johann Puschel Printmaker: Johann Puschel Publisher:
  - Asia (JHH# 5635 / Enregistre# 1913) (Folder Portfolio 16)
  - Africa (JHH# 5636 / Enregistre# 1914) (Folder Portfolio 16)
  - America (JHH# 5637 / Enregistre# 1915) (Folder Portfolio 16)
  - Africa (JHH# 203 / Enregistre# 1916) (Folder Portfolio 16)
    18th Century German Etching, mezzotint
    Artist: Baumgartner Printmaker: J.I. Koch Publisher:
- Series XXIII: Allegorical, French
  - America (JHH# 1350 / Enregistre# 1920) (Folder Portfolio 17A)
  - L'Europe (JHH# 1434 / Enregistre# 1921) (Folder Portfolio 17A)
    19th Century French Etching, stipple
    Artist: Printmaker: Publisher: Ch. Bance
  - L'Asie (JHH# 1435 / Enregistre# 1922) (Folder Portfolio 17A)
  - L'Afrique (JHH# 1436 / Enregistre# 1923) (Folder Portfolio 17A)
  - L'Amerique (JHH# 1437 / Enregistre# 1924) (Folder Portfolio 17A)
  - L'Europe (JHH# 1595 / Enregistre# 1925) (Folder Portfolio 17A)
  - L'Asie (JHH# 1596 / Enregistre# 1926) (Folder Portfolio 17A)
  - L'Afrique (JHH# 1597 / Enregistre# 1927) (Folder Portfolio 17A)
  - Aperitif Pere Motte (JHH# 1680 / Enregistre# 1928) (Folder Portfolio 17A)
    19th Century Belgian Reproductive print
    Artist: Printmaker: Publisher: Gouwelloos
  - L'Amerique (JHH# 1713 / Enregistre# 1929) (Folder Portfolio 17A)
    19th Century French Etching, stipple, hand coloring
    Artist: Printmaker: Publisher: Noel freres
  - L'Europe (JHH# 1735 / Enregistre# 1930) (Folder Portfolio 17A)
    Artist: Printmaker: Laujol Publisher: Agustoni Donato
  - L'Asie (JHH# 1736 / Enregistre# 1931) (Folder Portfolio 17A)
  - L'Afrique (JHH# 1737 / Enregistre# 1932) (Folder Portfolio 17A)
  - L'Amerique (JHH# 1738 / Enregistre# 1933) (Folder Portfolio 17A)
  - L'Europe (JHH# 1857 / Enregistre# 1934) (Folder Portfolio 17A)
    19th Century French Stipple, Etching
    Artist: Printmaker: Publisher: Fontana
  - L'Asie (JHH# 1858 / Enregistre# 1935) (Folder Portfolio 17A)
  - L'Amerique (JHH# 1859 / Enregistre# 1936) (Folder Portfolio 17A)
  - L'Europe (JHH# 2010 / Enregistre# 1937) (Folder Portfolio 17A)
    19th Century French Stipple, engraving
    Artist: Printmaker: Publisher: Aumont
  - L'Asie (JHH# 2011 / Enregistre# 1938) (Folder Portfolio 17A)
  - L'Afrique (JHH# 2012 / Enregistre# 1939) (Folder Portfolio 17A)
  - L'Amerique (JHH# 2013 / Enregistre# 1940) (Folder Portfolio 17A)
  - L'Amerique (JHH# 2051 / Enregistre# 1941) (Folder Portfolio 17A)
    19th Century French Etching, roulette, hand coloring
    Artist: Cuisin[?] Printmaker: C. Roemild Publisher: Me. Ve. Turgis
  - Europe (JHH# 2534 / Enregistre# 1942) (Folder Portfolio 17A)
    Artist: Printmaker: Dopter Publisher: Dopter
  - Asia (JHH# 2535 / Enregistre# 1943) (Folder Portfolio 17A)
  - Afrique (JHH# 2536 / Enregistre# 1944) (Folder Portfolio 17A)
  - Amerique (JHH# 2537 / Enregistre# 1945) (Folder Portfolio 17A)
  - L'Amerique (JHH# 3112 / Enregistre# 1946) (Folder Portfolio 17A)
  - L'Amerique (JHH# 3126 / Enregistre# 1947) (Folder Portfolio 17B)
    19th Century French Stipple, etching
  - L'Amerique (JHH# 3151 / Enregistre# 1948) (Folder Portfolio 17B)
  - L'Europe (JHH# 3210 / Enregistre# 1949) (Folder Portfolio 17B)
    19th Century French Etching, roulette
    Artist: Cuisin ? Printmaker: Dopter Publisher: Me. Ve. Turgis
  - L'Asie (JHH# 3211 / Enregistre# 1950) (Folder Portfolio 17B)
    Artist: Cuisin ? Printmaker: C. Roemild Publisher: Me. Ve. Turgis
  - L'Afrique (JHH# 3212 / Enregistre# 1951) (Folder Portfolio 17B)
  - L'Amerique (JHH# 3213 / Enregistre# 1952) (Folder Portfolio 17B)
  - L'Europe (JHH# 3788 / Enregistre# 1953) (Folder Portfolio 17B)
    Artist: Printmaker: Publisher: Cereghetti
  - L'Asie (JHH# 3789 / Enregistre# 1954) (Folder Portfolio 17B)
  - L'Afrique (JHH# 3790 / Enregistre# 1955) (Folder Portfolio 17B)
  - L'Amerique (JHH# 3791 / Enregistre# 1956) (Folder Portfolio 17B)
  - L'Amerique (JHH# 3823 / Enregistre# 1957) (Folder Portfolio 17B)
    19th Century Italian Etching, aquatint, hand coloring
    Artist: Adolphe Monticelli Printmaker: Gallo Gallina Publisher:
  - Europe (JHH# 3982 / Enregistre# 1958) (Folder Portfolio 17B)
    Artist: Achille Jacques-Jean-Marie Deveria Printmaker: Alfred Léon Lemercier Publisher: Frederic Emile Jeannin
  - Asie (JHH# 3983 / Enregistre# 1959) (Folder Portfolio 17B)
    Artist: Achille Jacques Jean Marie Deveria Printmaker: Alfred Léon Lemercier Publisher: Frederic Emile Jeannin
  - Amerique (JHH# 3984 / Enregistre# 1960) (Folder Portfolio 17B)
  - L'Europe (JHH# 4021 / Enregistre# 1961) (Folder Portfolio 17B)
    19th Century French Stipple, engraving, hand coloring
    Artist: Vauthier Printmaker: Bertrand Publisher: Aumont
  - L'Asie (JHH# 4022 / Enregistre# 1962) (Folder Portfolio 17B)
  - L'Afrique (JHH# 4023 / Enregistre# 1963) (Folder Portfolio 17B)
  - L'Amerique (JHH# 4024 / Enregistre# 1964) (Folder Portfolio 17B)
  - L'Europe (JHH# 4159 / Enregistre# 1965) (Folder Portfolio 17B)
    Artist: Henri Grevedon Printmaker: Lemercier Publisher: Aumont
  - L'Asie (JHH# 4160 / Enregistre# 1966) (Folder Portfolio 17B)
  - Afrique (JHH# 4161 / Enregistre# 1967) (Folder Portfolio 17B)
  - Amerique (JHH# 4162 / Enregistre# 1968) (Folder Portfolio 17B)
  - America (JHH# 4211 / Enregistre# 1969), 1808 (Folder Portfolio 17B)
    19th Century English Roulette, hand coloring
    Artist: Printmaker: Publisher: St. Birm
  - L'Europe (JHH# 4680 / Enregistre# 1970) (Folder Portfolio 17B)
    19th Century French Roulette, hand coloring
  - L'Asie (JHH# 4681 / Enregistre# 1971) (Folder Portfolio 17B)
  - L'Afrique (JHH# 4682 / Enregistre# 1972) (Folder Portfolio 17B)
  - L'Amerique (JHH# 4683 / Enregistre# 1973) (Folder Portfolio 17B)
  - L'Europe (JHH# 4684 / Enregistre# 1974) (Folder Portfolio 17B)
    19th Century French Etching, aquatint, roulette
    Artist: Chasselat Printmaker: Nargeot Publisher: Tessari
  - L'Asie (JHH# 4685 / Enregistre# 1975) (Folder Portfolio 17B)
  - L'Afrique (JHH# 4686 / Enregistre# 1976) (Folder Portfolio 17B)
  - L'Amerique (JHH# 4687 / Enregistre# 1977) (Folder Portfolio 17B)
  - L'Amerique (JHH# 4688 / Enregistre# 1978) (Folder Portfolio 17C)
  - Lampe "Titus" (JHH# 4992 / Enregistre# 1979) (Folder Portfolio 17C)
    20th Century French Photographic reproduction
    Artist: Herouard Printmaker: Publisher: Camis
  - L'Europe (JHH# 5211 / Enregistre# 1980) (Folder Portfolio 17C)
    Artist: Printmaker: H. Cardon Publisher: Boulard
  - Amerique (JHH# 5388 / Enregistre# 1983) (Folder Portfolio 17C)
    Artist: Printmaker: Publisher: Codoni aine
  - L'Asie (JHH# 6291 / Enregistre# 1984) (Folder Portfolio 17C)
    Artist: Printmaker: Publisher: F. Dubreuil
  - L'Afrique (JHH# 6292 / Enregistre# 1985) (Folder Portfolio 17C)
  - L'Amerique (JHH# 6293 / Enregistre# 1986) (Folder Portfolio 17C)
  - L'Asie et ses parfums, les tresors de l'Afrique… (JHH# 6420 / Enregistre# 1987), 1719 (Folder Portfolio 17C)
    Artist: B. Picart Printmaker: B. Picarts Publisher:
  - L'Amerique (JHH# 6451 / Enregistre# 1988) (Folder Portfolio 17C)
    Artist: Laujol Printmaker: Laujol Publisher: Agustoni Donato
  - L'Europe (JHH# 6531 / Enregistre# 1989) (Folder Portfolio 17C)
    Artist: Achille Jacques Jean Marie Deveria Printmaker: Bénard Publisher: Aubert
  - L'Asie (JHH# 6532 / Enregistre# 1990) (Folder Portfolio 17C)
  - L'Afrique (JHH# 6533 / Enregistre# 1991) (Folder Portfolio 17C)
  - L'Amerique (JHH# 6534 / Enregistre# 1992) (Folder Portfolio 17C)
  - Mlle. Grassari (JHH# 6607 / Enregistre# 1993) (Folder Portfolio 17C)
    Artist: Alexandre-Marie Colin Printmaker: F. Noel Publisher: F. Noel
  - Europe (JHH# 7171 / Enregistre# 1994) (Folder Portfolio 17C)
    19th Century French Engraving, stipple
    Artist: Printmaker: Publisher: Noel
  - Asie (JHH# 7172 / Enregistre# 1995) (Folder Portfolio 17C)
  - Asie (JHH# 7173 / Enregistre# 1996) (Folder Portfolio 17C)
  - Amerique (JHH# 7174 / Enregistre# 1997) (Folder Portfolio 17C)
  - Europe (JHH# 7596 / Enregistre# 1998) (Folder Portfolio 17C)
  - Asie (JHH# 7597 / Enregistre# 1999) (Folder Portfolio 17C)
  - Afrique (JHH# 7598 / Enregistre# 2000) (Folder Portfolio 17C)
  - Amerique (JHH# 7599 / Enregistre# 2001) (Folder Portfolio 17C)
  - L'Afrique (JHH# 7630 / Enregistre# 2002) (Folder Portfolio 17C)
    Artist: Printmaker: L. Deshayes Publisher: L. Deshayes
  - L'Asie (JHH# 7651 / Enregistre# 2003) (Folder Portfolio 17C)
    Artist: Boissy Printmaker: Cheyère Publisher: Genty
  - L'Afrique (JHH# 7652 / Enregistre# 2004) (Folder Portfolio 17C)
  - La Bele Americaine de New York (JHH# 7720 / Enregistre# 2005) (Folder Portfolio 17C)
    Artist: Printmaker: Bosselman Publisher: Bulla
- Series XXIII: Historical, Dutch
  - America Vertrapt het Woedende Albion (JHH# 314 / Enregistre# 2006) (Folder Portfolio 18)
    19th Century Dutch Etching and engraving
    Artist: P. Wagenaar Printmaker: G. Brouwer Publisher: A. Borghers
  - Den Britsen Leopard tot Reden gebracht (JHH# 317 / Enregistre# 2007) (Folder Portfolio 18)
    18th? Century Dutch Etchings, hand coloring
    Artist: CatBatavus [?] Printmaker: Publisher:
  - America (JHH# 345 / Enregistre# 2008) (Folder Portfolio 18)
    18th? Century Dutch Engraving
    Artist: P. Sibrants Printmaker: P. Sibrants Publisher: D. Voskuns
  - Verklaaring van de Zinnebeeldige Konstplaat (JHH# 350 / Enregistre# 2009) (Folder Portfolio 18)
    18th? Century Dutch Etching, hand coloring
  - [Triumph of Louis XIV of France] (JHH# 1107 / Enregistre# 2010) (Folder Portfolio 18)
    Artist: Romeyn de Hooghe Printmaker: Romeyn de Hooghe Publisher: Johannem Leonardi
  - [Triumph of Louis XIV of France] (JHH# 1111 / Enregistre# 2011) (Folder Portfolio 18)
  - Americae Retectio (JHH# 6521 / Enregistre# 2012) (Folder Portfolio 18)
    Artist: Joannes Stradanus Printmaker: Adrianus Collaert Publisher: Philippe Galle
  - Christophorus Columbus Ligur (JHH# 6522 / Enregistre# 2013) (Folder Portfolio 18)
  - Americus Vespuccius Florentinus (JHH# 6523 / Enregistre# 2014) (Folder Portfolio 18)
  - Ferdinandes Magalanes Lusitanus (JHH# 6524 / Enregistre# 2015) (Folder Portfolio 18)
- Series XXIV: Mixed Prints
  - Europe (JHH# 10003 / Enregistre# 2016) (Folder Portfolio 19)
    Artist: Printmaker: L. Turgis Publisher: L. Turgis
  - Asia (JHH# 10004 / Enregistre# 2017) (Folder Portfolio 19)
  - Afrique (JHH# 10005 / Enregistre# 2018) (Folder Portfolio 19)
  - The Harbour of Tripoli (JHH# 10006 / Enregistre# 2019a) (Folder Portfolio 19)
    19th Century American Etching
    Artist: Printmaker: Edward Yeager Publisher:
  - [The Burning of the Philiadelphia] (JHH# 10007 / Enregistre# 2019b) (Folder Portfolio 19)
    19th Century American Mezzotint
    Artist: William Hamlin Printmaker: William Hamlin Publisher:
  - Capt. Sterrett in the Schooner Enterprise (JHH# 10008 / Enregistre# 2019c) (Folder Portfolio 19)
    Artist: M. Corne Printmaker: Publisher:
  - The Blowing up of the Frigate Philadelphia (JHH# 10009 / Enregistre# 2019d) (Folder Portfolio 19)
  - Decatur avenging the murder of his brother (JHH# 10010 / Enregistre# 2019e) (Folder Portfolio 19)
  - Decatur's Struggle with the Algerines (JHH# 10011 / Enregistre# 2019f) (Folder Portfolio 19)
    19th Century American Engraving
  - Decatur's Conflict with the Algerine at Tripoli (JHH# 10012 / Enregistre# 2019g) (Folder Portfolio 19)
    19th Century American Etching, roulette
    Artist: Printmaker: Publisher: Johnson, Fry & Co.
  - Brand der Philadelphia vor Tripolis (JHH# 10013 / Enregistre# 2019h) (Folder Portfolio 19)